What if I told you there is an AI system
that can launch complete brand with all
media assets in 30 minutes with true
banana a virtual brand I just created
from scratch in 30 minutes here's what
is going on this is our N system here
first you generate one image of your
brand or product here I created this one
and you fill out the information about
the product product description here if
you can see here product information,
basic style, lighting, palette, and
audience. All of your brand information,
essence, promise, tone of voice,
positioning. Once you're ready, you can
generate avatars and then our AI system
will vive it and generate three
different avatars based on your brand
TNA. Let me show you this one. And in
avatar, the system created four
different actors, including this Bigfoot
style mask code. And if you look at
here, we have very detailed description
so that you can always change it and
regenerate until you like these avatars,
ethnicity, age, even age, range, gender,
everything phys.
So next step is to create assets. So
again our AI system can generate
multiple assets with one click. You go
to product you can generate here
generate asset ideas AI will generate
multiple ideas. It create a five of them
from there with one click again you can
generate images. So even like this text
overlay and here true banana I like this
one and I like this one. The great part
of the system is most times you are
struggling with the image prompt. Our AI
system will autogenerate prompt
following all of your important
information such as brain DNA, the
style, lighting, settings, everything.
And here it was autogenerated. You can
even click again to generate UGC video
or general product showcase video. Here,
let me show you the outcome. I've tried
a lot of detail, but true banana is
something else. It's the real deal. I
didn't even touch the video prompt which
is created in one shot by our AI systems
and it created this viral like video
agency quite the same kind of package.
They can charge a lot of money in 3 week
timeline. I launched this true banana
yesterday morning taking only 30
minutes. And the best part is I can
create it unlimited times few clicks and
I can generate unlimited variations for
us and images. So, if you like to try
this one, comment banana.